Guide to the Anthony Edward Siegman Papers SC1171
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Anthony Edward Siegman papers
1916-2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Siegman, Anthony E.
SC1171
53.25 Linear Feet
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of administrative files, research files, correspondence, and publications.
Biographical / Historical
Anthony Siegman was an electrical engineer, primarily focused on masers and lasers. Siegman earned an AB from Harvard in 1952, the MS in Applied Physics from the University of California at Los Angeles in 1954, and a Ph.D. in Electrical Engineering from Stanford University in 1957. Siegman became an assistant professor at Stanford in Electrical Engineering in 1957. In 1964 he was promoted to full professor, and retired from his Stanford position as the Burton J. and Ann M. McMurtry Professor of Engineering in November 1998. He was president of the Optical Society of America in 1999 and was awarded the Esther Hoffman Beller Medal in 2009.
Lasers.; Masers.; Electrical engineering -- Study and teaching.; Siegman, Anthony E.
- Administrative files
  - IAG Planning, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - IAG Planning, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alkali Lasers, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clemson JTO Projects, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cavity Pulse Enhancement, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mirage Pumping, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Glass & Dopant Data, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Pumping Schemes, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hollow Waveguide Lasers, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gain-Guided Fiber Modes Josa A, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fiber Laser Gain/Pwr Analysis, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fiber Laser Refs, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Step Fiber Laser Calcs, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - G-G Fiber Mode Analysis, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gain-Guider Fiber Lasers (OSA), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fiber Laser, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Gain-Guided Fiber Lasers, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fiber Lasers: Southampton, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Fiber Lasers: Laser Energetics, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Fiber Laser Fab. & Doping, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - IAG Refs, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - IAG Rods, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: IAG, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Pubs: Other IAG, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Presentations: IAG, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Presentations (Old), 2008 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Fiber Laser Writeups, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - IAG Pubs, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - IAG Pubs, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Presentations, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - GG Fiber Modes, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Step Fiber Mode Analysis, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Refs (New), 2008 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - OPN Fresnel Lenserf OPN, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Fresnel Lenserf Opn, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Evanescent Gain, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Evanescent Gain Projects, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Inhomog. PWs, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2003-2011 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Hovic/ Ignatovich, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Klaus-Leeb, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Kostenbauder, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Intro, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Goos-Haenchen, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Designer Fibers, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ABCD Matrices, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - AOP Review/Tutorial, 2008, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Planar WG Modes, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fourier Series Calculations, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - TIR Pilots, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - OWG REES, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ANICIN, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Doerr, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Hankel Transforms, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Klaus & Leeb, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Schwetel, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - SLAB WG Pert. Calcs, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - SLAB WG Mode Analysis, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Planar WG Antiguided, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Gaussian Ducts, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Gauss Ducts/ Pert. Stability Refs, 1968, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Duplaa, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - BPM Calculations, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Layered WG Analysis, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Absolut Optics, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Agilent Admin., 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Agilent Docs, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Agilent Notes, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Aurora CTO Mtg., March 2001 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Beam: The Race to Make the Laser, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Arizona/OSC, April 2009 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - BSTJ Online, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Lecture, December 2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cincinnati: Geo, Batta, November 2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - CIOMP, Einstein Prof., 2010 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - CLEO/IQEC, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CLEO, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - CLEO/ Plenary, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Creol Academic Review, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Creol Visit, April 2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Creol Visit, April 2004 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - CSICOP, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Directed Energy Solns (Hartwick), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Drivers Licence, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - EE Dept, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - EIPBN Mtg, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Emcore v. Avago, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Meeting/Conference Notes, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Erlangen Imprs Review, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Erlangen Imprs Review, 2010 Dec (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Erlangen Advisory Board, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Erlangen Report, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Max Planck Institute Scientific Report, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - ESC: Admin, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Europhoton - Paris, 2008 Sep (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Falco Affair, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Falco Inquiry, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Falco, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Gamo Born Nomination, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ginzton Memoir/Refs, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Harris Awards, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Teklicon, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hawaii Trip, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Graham, Robert K, 1940-1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kapitan Man - Admin, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Kapitan Man: Depo & Trial, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Koc Univ, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Kawata, 2001 Aug., 2009 July (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mathematica Rants, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Mathematica Notes, 2009 March (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Modular Lasers, 2002 June 5 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - MS Reviews, 2009 July 21-23 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Medical/VHS, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NAE/NAS, 2009-2010 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - NAS Election 2011 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - News of the Universe, 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - News of the Universe (2), 1982-1984, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Nutter: Motes, 1971, 1991, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Nutter Admin, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Nutter Invoices, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Optics Trivia Bowl, 2005-2006, 2010 April (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - OSA Honorary Members, 2009-2011 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Parrondo Paradox, 1999-2000, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Passengers As Packets, 2005, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Patents: Morris Expert Witness Course, 2002, 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Patents System for the 21st Century, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Patents, 1972-1978, 1984,1990, 2004-2011 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Patents: Lemley, Morris, 2002, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Patents (2), 2004-2005, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Patent Reform, 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Patents: Laser Cat Exerciser, 1995 Aug., 2007 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Patent Report NAE, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Patents (3), 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Fiber Laser Patent, 1997-2003, 2006 April (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - PG&E, 1997, 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Pillsbury, Arthur C., 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Religion & Science, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - SCRL Board, 2007-2012 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - SCRL Annual MTG (Wed. 18 May), 2006-2007, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - SCRL Lease Creep, 1996, 2003-2005, 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - SCRL Lease Creep-Docs, 1999, 2002, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - SCRL Broadband: Clearwire, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SCRL Docs, 2001-2005, 2010 Oct. 20 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Frost, etc. 1952, 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - SHS Excursions?, 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - SHS Oral Histories, 2011 June (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - SHS House Tour 2011 (empty folder) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - SHS Board 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - A Chronology of Stanford University and its Founders, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - SHS Pubs Comm, 2005-2011 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - SHS Board, 2004-2011 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - SPRC Annual, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - SPRC (Stanford Photonics Res. Ctr.), 2003, 2005, 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - SPRC 2011 Annual Symposium Proceedings & Annual Report (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - SPRC Symposium (empty folder), 2011 Sept. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Stoicheff, 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Imaging IR Guidance Panel, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - AF Scientific Advisory Board, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - ACE, 1974 June 24 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - ARPA Memory Program, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Visitor: Belanger, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Blanaru, Constantin, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Car. Educ. Res. Found, 28673 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Chemistry Dpeartment Industrial Affiliates Symposium, 1975 Spring (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Chinese Laser Delegation, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - CLEA, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - CLEA, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CLEA Meeting, 1973 June (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Dynamical Processes Conference - Madison, WI, 1979 June (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Hardy, Dr. Amos, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - IEEE Awards Committee, Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - IEE Awards Guide: An Invitation to Nominate, 1973 Nov (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Stanford University Operating Budget Guidelines, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - EE Finance Committee, Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Education, Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - EE Department, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Exec Comm, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - NASA Outstanding Scientist Award A.E. Siegman and S.E. Harris, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - EE Excom, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - IXth. Internation Conference on Quantum Electronics, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - QE Conference, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - IQEC - Atlanta, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - IQEC Conference Amsterdam, 1976 June (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - AFSAB: Engr. & Sci. Manpower Committee Meeting #1, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - IQEC Conference, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - IQEC Conference, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 6th Winter QE Conference - Steamboat, 1976 Feb (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Jobs, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Kunz, Dr. Kaiser S., 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Education: Visual Aids, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Engineering, School of, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - School of Engineering, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Letokhov, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - ERDA E(29-2)-3605 Contract Information and Letters, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - A.E. Siegman Correspondence, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - ERDA E(29-2)-3605 Internal Memorandum Ginzton Lab. Report No. 2977, 1979 June (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - ERDA E(29-2)-3605 Progress Reports and Final Report, 1977 Jan (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ERDA E(29-2)-3605 GL Report No. 2599, 1976 July (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - ERDA E(29-2)-3605 Research Proposal to ERA "Optical Resonator and Beam Studies", 1976 May (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - ERDA E(29-2)-3605 Progress Report/G.L. Report 2548, 1976 March (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - ERDA E(29-2)-3605 Quarterly Progress Report/G.L. 2472, 1975 Sept (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - ERDA E(29-2)-3605 Proposal to LASL Optical Resonator and Beam Studies, 1975 May (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - NASA NGL-05-020-103 Semiannual Status Report/GL 2664, 1977 Feb (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - NASA NGL-05-020-103 Semiannual Status Report/GL 2607, 1976 Aug (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - NGL-05-020-103 Renewal Proposal to NASA Headquarters Studies on Lasers and Laser Devices, 1975 Feb (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - LASL XP5-72553-1 Final Report (EY-76-S-03-0326), 1978 April (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - LASL XP5-72553-1 Final Report, 1976 Nov (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - LASL XP5-72553-1 Research Proposal ERDA (Los Alamos) Ultrashort Pulses at CO2 Laser Wavelengths, 1976 Aug (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - LASL XP5-72553-1 Revised Proposal/Special Research Support Agreement - "Ultrashort Pulses at CO2...", 1976 Jan (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - LASL XP5-72553-1 Special Research Support Agreement "Ultrashort Pulses at CO2 Laser Wavelengths", 1976 Jan (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - LASL XP5-72553-1 Special Research Support Agreement (Proposal) "Ultrashort Pulses at CO2 Laser Wavelengths", 1975 Oct (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - LASL XP5-72553-1 Renewal Proposal to LASL "Ultrashort Pulses at CO2 Laser Wavelengths", 1975 March (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - LASL XP5-72553-1 Final Report, 1975 Aug (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - LASL XP5-72553-1 First Semiannual Progress Report, 1975 Jan (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - NSF ENG74-03433 Final Scientific Report, 1977 March (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NSF GK-4372X Request for Second-Year Funding, 1975 Jan (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - N00014-75-C-0632 (JSEP) GL Report 3052 (Manuscript) "Pulse Stretching in a Q-Switch", 1979 Nov (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - N00014-75-C-0632 (JSEP) GL Report 3051 (Manuscript) "Phase Conjugate Reflection", 1979 Oct (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - JSEP Report, 1979 Aug (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - JSEP Report, 1978 Sept (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - JSEP Report, 1977 Sept (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - JSEP Report, 1976 Aug (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - JSEP Report, 1975 Aug (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - NSF: GK 32371X1, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NSF: PSEC Optical Measurements, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NASA: NGL-05-020-103 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - AFOSR: F44620-69-C-0017, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - AFPSR: F44620-71-C-0053, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - AF 53, 1975 Jan (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - AFOSR 76-70, 1976 Jan-Dec (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - AFPSR: Knausenberg-3043 Supplemental Proposal, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - ERDA/SRSA Meeting, 1976 Apr (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - ERDA/SRSA Meeting, 1975 Aug (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - ERDA/LASL #3 - CO2 Short Pulses, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - ERDA/LASL #2 - CO2 Short Pulses, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - ERDA/LASL #1 - CO2 Short Pulses, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - ERDA: Resonator SRSA, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - ERDA: Resonator SRSA #2, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Wolfram Schmid, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - SGES, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Search Committee: Dean of Grad Students, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Sandia Lecture Series on Lasers, 1973 Jan (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Robert Shea, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Shmaonov, Tigran, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - TAC, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - TAC, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - TAC, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - TTG Descriptive, Participants, Status Reports, etc, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - UARL Laser Advisory Group, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - ARCO Visit, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Wang, Dr. S.C. Personal (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - AES Family Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - AES Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - AES Archives, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - AES History/Archives, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Battery Heights, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - American Express, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Aurora Admin., 2009 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Bent Science, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Carnelian Woods, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Carr McClellan, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - DSHS, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Donner Summit Hist Soc, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Erlangen, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Erlangen-Albrecht-DDR, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - To Stanf Library Archive, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Chodorow, Marvin, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ginzton/Stanford Mag, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Ginzton Memoir V.I.O., 2005 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Ginzton Memoir: Final, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Ginzton Memoir: SLAC History, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Ginzton Security Clearance Flap, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - MIT 150, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Ginzton Lab, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Ginzton Lab History, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Ginzton Lab, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Ginzton/HEPL/SLAC Chronology, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Working Draft of Lasers Textbook, circa 1985 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - ENF, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - ENF Linear Systems, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - ENF Measurement, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - ENF Refs, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - ENF Refs, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Excess Noise Expt., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - ENF: NonNormal OPS & Pseudospectra, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - ENF/ SM Analyses, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - ENF Notes, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - ENF Expt., 1986-1998 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Polarization Eigen Modes, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Newspaper articles, etc.), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - NBS Panel, May 1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - A.E. Siegman Correspondence, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - SAB Ad Hoc. Comm. on Sci & Engr. Manpower, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - AFSAB: Ramstein Meeting, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - NBS Panel, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting Opticalm Society of America - Toronto, Canada, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Affiliates: Annual Review, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Affiliates Program: General, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - S.S. Affiliates Titles/Speakers, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - S-S Affiliates, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - S-S Affiliates Program, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - AFSAB: Research and Geophysics Panel, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - AFSAB: Past Meetings, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Loose Papers, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Outlines, 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Toby Mansuripur, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Resonators, circa 1990s (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Transparencies from Talks: Re Beam Quality etc., undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Uns. Res. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - SEICOLS: Frequency Domain Non-linear Optical Measurement of Femtosecond Relaxation- Trebino, Barker and Siegman, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 7th International Conference on LASER Spectroscopy - Maui, Hawaii, June 24-28 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Julie - MBE, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Fouquet/Siegman: Picosecond Electronics and Optoelectronics, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Top. Meeting on PSec Electron. and Optoelectronics - Fouquet & Siegman, March 1985 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Julie- MOCVD, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Frequency Bandwidths, etc. - Trebino/ Siegman: Optics Commun, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Trebino/ Siegman, "Freq. Bandwidths in Nondegen. N-wave-mixing interactions and Ind.-grating-Geoms, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Design Considerations - Laser Resonators - Variable Refl. Mirrors - Siegman, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Fourth-Order Partial Coherence Effects - Trebino, Gustafson, Siegman, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Bibliography Resonator and Beam Calculation, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - "Rise-Fall Ambiguity" - Optics Ltrs & Ultrafast, July 1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - A Fast Diffusion-Driven Photodetector: Theory and Experiment, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Axial Modes in a Grating-Dispersed Laser Cavity - AES (Appl. Phys. B), 1987 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - High-speed diffusion-driven photodetector, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Life on the Skew AES. Comp. in Phys., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 168 Bipolar Bimodal Fiber Optic, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - OSA Tutorial, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Phase Conj. in Polysilanes, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - "Excess Spontaneous emission in non-hermitian optical systems I. laser amplifiers", 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - "Excess Spontaneous emission in non-hermitian optical systems II. laser oscillators", 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - "Excess Spontaneous emission in variable-reflexivity-mirror lasers (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - "Defining and measuring laser beam quality: the M2 factor", 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - "Frequency-domain observation of the ultrafast intertial response of the optical Kerr effect in CS2", 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - AES/SPIE "New Developments", 1990 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - R.V. Pole Lecture, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Macleod Gainy Coatings, Fiber Cauities, Emails, Patents, 2008-2010 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Ted Maiman, 1960-1961,2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Self Fourier Funcs - I, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Self-Fourier Funcs - II, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ENF (Excess Noise Factor) REFs, 1984,1988-1990, 1999- 2004 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Tureci, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Hamburg Trip, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - CLEO/QELS (Baltimore), 2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Liekki, 2006 April (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Kaist Eac, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Sick AG Patent/Coats, 1995, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - AES Desktop, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Refracted Beams, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Pulsed plane Wave Solns, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Inhomg PW Notes, 2003 Oct. 14-15 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Pulsed Plane Wave Profiles: Quartic-Gaussian, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - KG Vector Equations KGV 001, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Poynting Vector Thm., 2011 July 20 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Finite Width Beams, 2004 Nov.-Dec. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - GOOS Haenchen, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Layered Fresnel, 2004, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Tapered Gain Media, 2011 May 28 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Gaussian Ducts, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Fresnel Refl. Analysis, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Fresnel & Lenserf Refl., 2007 Autumn (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Fresnel Reflect. & TIR, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Stadium Diode Lasers, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Kpstemnaider.Sim.AES, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - NATO Workshop On Res., Smolenice, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - UPoN [Adelaide], 1999 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Vision 2000, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - JSTQE Millennium Issue/Resonations, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Shanghai Talk, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - SPIE MTG, San Diego, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Virtual Source, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - BQ Handbook, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Cheng and AES "Quantum ENF", 2003 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Citation Classics, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Phototube Patent, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - FM Patent, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Lamp Patent, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - ARR Patent, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Rise-Fall ambiguities..Nonlin-optical Trebino, Barker, Kostenbauder, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Rise-Fall Ambiguities..Ultraf-mezs Trebino, Barker, Kostembauder, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Ray-Pulse Matrices, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Nemes, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Nemes, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Grepstad and Starr, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Dolven, Jeff, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Brad Kondraki, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Renters: Wm Tronzo Howard Ste, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - James Clifford, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Martin Berger, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Studio: David Marriot, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Gone, Joe, 2011-2012 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Renters JSB Johan, Elberskog, 2011-2012 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Renters JSB Backer, Carolyn, 2011-2012 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Hillview Studio Allan V. Horwitz, 2012-2013 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Howard STE Yuma Totani, 2012-2013 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Cheryl Galvin, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Wendy Jones Howard St, 2004-2006 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Hillview Studio and wrapup, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Studio, Hill View David Marriot, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - JSB Subgroup, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - JSB PHII Public Comment, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - JSB Gup Mitigations, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)